Guide to the Uris Library Media Archive,1969-1991.
Uris Library Media Archive,1969-1991.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Uris Library Media Archive, 1969-1984.
13-6-3188
Cornell University.Uris Library,
76 video tapes, 25 reels of 16mm film, 2 DVDs.
Videos
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Video tapes relating to art, library and various lectures; 4 different video formats are represented in the collection.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Video tapes relating to art, government, library and various lectures; 4 different video formats are represented in the collection.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.
Subjects:
Student activities--New York (State)--Ithaca.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Aristoph, n.d.; Video-10 [10, 37, 59] (Box 1)
- Sheridan, n.d.; Video-37 (Box 1)
- Wycherley, The Humane City, n.d.; Video-59 (Box 1)
- Auburn St. Prison, n.d.; Video-34 [34, 128, 12] (Box 1)
- Ukranian Dance, n.d.; Video-128 (Box 1)
- William Kunstler: Vietnam War discussion, 1971; Video 12 (Box 1)
- Chinese Opera, n.d.; Video-13 [13, 36, 73] (Box 1)
- Seeger Pt.2 of 2, Video-36 (Box 1)
- Seeley, n.d.; Video-73 (Box 1)
- The Line, n.d.; Video-19 (Box 1)
- The Line, n.d.; Video-19 (Box 1)
- Sturgeon, n.d.; Video-25 (Box 1)
- 1st part of Video-36, n.d.; Video-36 (Box 1)
- COSEP faculty discussion, 1971; Video-23 (Box 1)
- COSEP, Approach or Result?, 1971; Video-24 (Box 1)
- Auburn Concentration Camp, n.d.; Video-34 (Box 1)
- See Video-13, Video-36 (Box 1)
- See Video-10, Video-37 (Box 1)
- Sheridan, n.d.; Video-37 [37, 90, 94, 19] (Box 1)
- Ibsen, n.d.; Video-90 (Box 1)
- Gilgamesh, n.d.; Video-94 (Box 1)
- Ferro-[Cement]Concrete Boat. Also on DVD-593, n.d.; Video-40 (Box 1)
- R. D. Lang [sic. Laing] Book Knots. Also on DVD-593, n.d.; Video-41 (Box 1)
- Berrigan Weekend-America is Hard to Find. Also on DVD-593, 1970; Video-42 (Box 1)
- Building the Library's Collection, n.d.; Video-47 (Box 1)
- Ferro-[Cement]Concrete Boat, n.d.; Video-49 (Box 1)
- Merce Cunningham Dance Performance, n.d.; Video-52 (Box 1)
- See Video-10, Video-59 (Box 1)
- George McGovern, 1976; Video-66 (Box 1)
- Dr. Cade and the Peregrin Falcon, n.d.; Video-70 (Box 1)
- Jason Seley, n.d.; Video-73 (Box 1)
- Betsy Damon Women's Art Movement, n.d.; Video-76 (Box 2)
- Johnson Art Museum, 1984; Video-78 [78, 124] (Box 2)
- Images of and by Women of the 19th and 20th Century., n.d.; Video-124 (Box 2)
- Rosemary and H. Alexander Harms, n.d.; Video-89 (Box 2)
- See Video-37, Video-90 (Box 1)
- Betsy Rankin, n.d.; Video-91 (Box 2)
- Ellen Saltonstall, Rosemary Harms, n.d.; Video-92 (Box 2)
- P. Lawler Dance, 1974; Video-93 (Box 2)
- H. Alexander, 1973; Video-93 (Box 2)
- See Video 37, Video-94 (Box 1)
- "Hot Water," S. Marcuse, Cayuga Station Pt. 2, 1979; Video-100 (Box 2)
- Jay Saunders Redding Interview, 1984; Video-106 (Box 2)
  -Use DVD-991&992 instead of video cassette
- 4 Artists Talk: Isabel Bishop, Philip Pearlstein, Lucas Saranis, and Richard Tuttle, 1974; Video-107 (Box 2)
- Three Dances, 1973; Videos-110 [110, 109, 120] (Box 2)
- Mother Mallard's Portable Masterpiece lecture demonstration, 1975; Video-109 (Box 2)
- C. U. Play, n.d.; Video-120 (Box 2)
- Judy Chicago Talks About Her Work, 1972; Video-113 (Box 2)
- A Century of the C. U. Libraries, n.d.; Video-114 (Box 2)
- Hans Bethe/Barry Commoner Pt. 1, 1977; Video-115 (Box 2)
- Hans Bethe/Barry Commoner Pt. 2, 1977; Videos-115 [15, 64] (Box 2)
- Mr. Spock, n.d.; Video-64 (Box 2)
- Character of American Nation Pt. 1, 1977; Video-118 (Box 2)
- See Video-110, Video-120 (Box 2)
- Reminiscences of Cornell University Libraries: Bishop-Shepherd-Kaser, n.d.; Video-121 (Box 3)
- Non-violence, n.d.; Video-122 (Box 3)
- See Video-78, Video-124 (Box 2)
- See Video-34, Video-128 (Box 3)
- Fourth Annual Fun In The Sun, 1978; Video-137 (Box 3)
- Vietnam Revisited, n.d.; Video-141 (Box 3)
- Cornell University Library - circulation, n.d.; Video-170 (Box 3)
- Isabel Letelier, n.d.; Video-171 (Box 3)
- Jason Seley in His Studio, 1969; Video-281 (Box 3)
- Is There Life Beyond a Government Major?, n.d.; Video-368 (Box 3)
- Anti-War Rally (Jane Fonda, Thomas Hayden, Molly Near), October 14, 1972, 1972; Video-5543 (Box 3)
- CUL orientation for international students, 1991; Video-10526 (Box 3)
- "Who Cares?" Cayuga Station Part 1, Undated; V-11184 (Box 4)
- "Hot Water" Cayuga Station Part 2, 1976-05-18; V-11185 (Box 4)
- "Speaking Out" Cayuga Station Part 3, 1975-06; V-11186 (Box 4)
  Community representatives and organizers talk about the problems of participating in public hearings on utility and energy issues.
- #2, Undated; V-11187 (Box 4)
- Woyzeck, Video AV 6 2 of 2, 1970-10-11; V-11188 (Box 4)
- Woyzeck, Video AV 6 1 of 2, Undated; V-11189 (Box 4)
- Isabel Letecier, Video 171, 1978-02-23; V-11190 (Box 4)
- Jane Fonda Anti-war rally, Video AV 54 1 of 2, Undated; V-11191 (Box 4)
- Jane Fonda Anti-war rally, Video AV 54 2 of 2, Undated; V-11192 (Box 4)
- No Lecture/Demonstration Barnes Hall, Video AV 153 1 of 2, 1978-04-28; V-11193 (Box 4)
- No Lecture/Demonstration Barnes Hall, Video AV 153 2 of 2, 1978-04-28; V-11194 (Box 4)